[music]
Loot Ashoka
that a
[music]
that is
That
Welcome reader, welcome to the panel.
And
Rough you will share this with everyone
Today you are going to share your success story.
You're welcome and now we're big
I am eagerly listening to your story and
You will remain in the like and you will share it now.
And Arabi Sarkar Dada, you turn on your video.
keep this way
If needed, there is some snowfall of Pathak ji.
Whatever you have to do, you are in the office.
I and my video will be off then I will
I may post it on my channel now.
If you go, you
[music]
where am i at right now next voice reader
that a pradeep pradeep whatsapp me host
Make it all
Well, he was in the middle for some reason.
It has become useful, sir reader, you can start it.
Yes and theirs, you can unmute it, thank you.
you sir
Yes
Thank you very much sir, thank you very much
Many many salutations to you early in the morning
I got to see this and got to hear it.
To all colleagues on the panel To all colleagues
Hello and thank you to all of you
Friends, you spare your precious time
I had the opportunity to speak here.
through people so thanks to me
It seems that something is time and you
I hope that this is the time for everyone
That will be your investment and whatever I
You do it at home
that you see only in Gujjars the whole
And if I have a little bit of it too
If my words are beneficial then I will automatically
considers himself quite lucky
Because it is a good fortune to be in this app.
It's the same thing but those good people
Meet with good people after hearing all this
Things I really liked about this business man
once more definitely in the morning
There is time and we who wake up in the morning get it.
If we talk then all the people who are in the morning
You certainly deserve congratulations
Everyone not only joined but also understood you.
Those who attend here with interest
section and this lead essence member again
I will say that our mentor is Mahaguru Nursing.
Karwa was done to Sharad and all the top leaders
Who has created such a platform
Common people with respect are successful in the platform.
and are not only successful but also
Many people have to go further to be successful
I will give you inspiration and thank you very much.
I salute Narsi Karwa Sir and Sanjay Jain.
Sir, our top mental
He considered me worthy of this and gave me this
I made it worthy that I present something to you today.
I will be able to keep things and whatever I have said in this
I have felt it in business, I have felt it
that this business has been done which is done with currency
I got things whatever I am
I am only on the strength of if I can think about myself
If I say, today everything is mine only for
The reason is that when we people think only about money
₹100 or whatever I got
through our seniors that deserve it I
I have been able to become one and today I will try to make you
I will share that experience with you people.
I can express my thoughts through the use of lights.
I will keep it or
had happened
Jhaal
Our
Friends, I am Amit Pathak, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh.
I belong to and I want to come to this app
Soon after it was so wonderful that I
I can say it is the best movement of my life
They started just after I came in and
Earlier in Bilaspur University
I used to work in Embassy Electronics
I did it and then I went to university.
The network had started working and a
I came from a very middle class family.
I have started my journey before taking up this business.
The same hardship and poverty of my family
My father used to work, my father had 6 brothers.
All these things are shown in the government department.
When I used to work, there was a whole room in my house.
Meaning of family and great craze for job
and I was taught that as well
You are very happy to click on
Get your degree and get a good job.
So I just came in today to see how I
I will share about it as well.
But first I want to thank you
Thank you is important, we all should not forget it.
Whichever God they believe in knowingly or unknowingly
There is God, Allah, Jesus, in whomever
We definitely agreed in life that your breasts.
I wish God would give me one chance in life
I have a chance to do something big.
I think you all have seen this at some point
You must have prayed, what do you say friends?
We will do it, it is very nice, everyone asked for it artificial
If it happens and you still ask for it, I will tell you that.
Give thanks to the one above, why do you
The opportunity has been given, the opportunity has been given
So that you can make yourself your own
I hope you too are going to become a truly special person.
Such a company should be formed only for
I would like to thank you now that today India
This is the number one company in direct selling.
This is a big deal because thousands of companies
You have thousands of sorrows, it works but
Being number 1 is a big deal.
And not once has the coat been in use for more than 20 years.
for a long time and in that too in one thing
Surely the number of couples and even greater than being
I feel that everyone's turn will come soon.
lag behind, but more importantly
It is clearly the most trustworthy company.
Friends, I would like to thank you very much
To the company that I am in the most trusted company
I joined for the first time in my life.
Direct Selling Industry Network
Joined Marketing and most trusted
I have joined the company today.
It is a leading company in India and is trusted.
You see together
that the best year in a row
This is the best year, needless to say.
The most itemized ones are the oldest
Timers are most loved from India and abroad
April Luxury Car All these things automatically
But it tells that consecutive numbers and only
The company is here, the leaders are at sister's place.
But the people who work are at the top
Leadership is what I'm talking about from the beginning, Doctor.
From Top Neeraj to everyone did such work
Did that all the achievers are also number one only?
Everyone who works at the company
Direct Seller Veer is the best in his field
Good job and thanks for that
Our five great directors are the faces of all of us
But today, respectable to all of us, no matter how much he
Just thank you, that's all I can say.
complete that I my animated show
I think it will be less but five
Cancelled because of people friends like me we
drought and many people whose lives are very
How are they changing rapidly?
Gave a platform and a place of trust
over the direct selling industry, whether it
Friends, today I am joking about the income plan.
Answer: It's been 20 years, more than 20 years, if you
If you talk, take out the rare thousand in the middle.
It's been so wonderful for over a week now
The ribbon worked so well that our director
Sir, people said that one wife belongs to someone else.
The cheque does not stop and is very big in itself.
It happens that we see people talking
I have a lot of faith in the government and in government jobs.
Many government employees are on strike.
You will sit and have sex every day, whether it's mine
I haven't received my salary or bonus.
Then the promotion came out but thanks soft
In 21 years of directorship, he has earned thousands
It hasn't happened for more than a week now.
No one has received a check, it's great for this
We deserve applause, we have five more great ones.
Actually this is the thinking behind these matters
Companions trustworthy toxic bar consumption most
Trustworthy because in this industry we
to your friends to your relatives
To brother, to sister, to special people,
We make a dress and if it goes wrong somewhere by mistake
If the place is gone then that company closes down and
We've seen this a lot over the years.
Then people get disappointed directly.
I start to hate sailing, but only
An industry where you and I are proud
can proudly bring anyone from
Not only by getting him to join only on
You can give the product by joining but also
He could have made her a career that today I and
You are sitting here spinal us me so
I am confident that for many years to come
Maybe the elders will go and our children will
All the shortages will continue
But this will be the weight of five directors.
How nice that it only works at that time.
Our great guru Naresh will remain so trustworthy
Naresh Agarwal Sachin It always keeps us curious
Whichever company you come from, you get good things.
Please tell me about what you get
I will talk about the small trust I have in my
Let me talk about home recently.
Some product details cannot be messaged
Yes, I would like to tell you, but I am also starting
Let me tell you once, when we
Let's talk if we go near someone
Let's talk about products only in
I will talk about syrup Chandi somewhere else.
I don't talk to my friends at home.
About two and a half years ago, my father-in-law came to my house.
Ji was diagnosed with lung cancer and
Everyone was very scared, everyone was very worried.
Because you all know about cancer
Getting very scared on hearing the name
It was said that there is no cure for it.
Things happen but let me tell you this
I just don't have to be so confident that I
I heard them at work outside.
The company went to many speakers for employment.
Sanyukt and there I met my father-in-law Kunoli
Love should start at that time and whatever
What actually remains after treatment
There are treatments for cancer that
Chemotherapy, all these things happen to him
Later people's fists become very tight.
People cancer comes again and again but only
The gift level products we offer
Our directors are proudly giving it
You can say who lives in my house
Living proof is that since then I have had Noni
The doctor started giving him so many
World Multivitamins and Around the World
I gave the product and left the rabbit
But for my father-in-law, only Noni
used it and then this is the result
that every three to four months an abdominal scan
By doing something, terminology which is known throughout
Body cancer they say drinking normally
Due to this, Noni gave such good results that
Any symptoms of any cancer now
The problems have just disappeared from their lives.
And just by using Noni regularly
Friends, such a company, such a director who
It gives us so many wonderful and life-giving things
No shopping complexes, when scooters are given away
Such directors are looting our company.
are doing and we all certainly wish well
That's why I got a chance to talk to them
I will invest our money
Mahaguru Shri Sanjay Jain Sir who is here today
It is at the level that one has to find their level
Friends, did you ever come to all of us?
Everyone is becoming a diamond, but I taught this to them.
Down is our great Sanjay Sir, our great
May Sanjay Sir's achievements be like this, friends.
He spent so many days here working for this company
I designed the system so that
He not only succeeded but also inspired people to succeed.
I lined up for this, don't be such a duplicate
system was created and I have seen Sir that
The most difficult things are easily
are visible and this is the reason why this business
Even the biggest tasks are accomplished by ordinary people like us.
Easily doing the going city for the company
had to bring in new inspections to make the city Diamond
After that, the more speed I increased, the more I focused on everything.
that this connection change we also behind the condition
They run away and these shy people remain such ideals
that connection runs after them
Alarm Mercury IS in the whole only Sir
No achievement was gone after that the mother of the next
On account of Anand Sir Universal Convent
By going to such a great Mahaguru, we will
Everyone is lucky because friends
The Guru-Shishya tradition is the identity of our country.
It has been there and every child here knows it.
Guru has the status of God and even above that.
I've definitely rated it that way
We have such a mentor with us, Mr. Sanjay
Jain Sir, I salute you and support you.
Quiet stores whenever I see them
Our senior Narsi can really do it myself
I am so excited that I will come and give you some fun.
Let me tell you this much after listening to Sir
I got excited that I want you right now
Let me tell you, this is the first time we heard this.
So I said to you on one side
It happened after getting up from the seat and this is a big thing.
People of friends will have sad and unhappy lives
I am living in the one you will meet Nittu
He will talk to you about your problems.
He will talk to you in a way that will encourage you.
He will not talk but will get the body nursed.
I thanked you like this sir, you are looking angry
By doing this our power increases many times.
When you gave me the opportunity to speak at the beginning
So the recording comes a message, not this
Panel Recording Form so you do
Would like to go to the Got Talent website
I had to call him so I went to the cost
Seeing the effect, there is pain in one side
That your achievements are also like this
You have the ultimate, but you are also human.
So good that whenever any person from you
If that man gets hundred percent, how much
Dena Pushpendra and Jharkhand will also be weakened
So this will definitely kill the Tiger Group.
When he comes out, the mentor
You can see the interest in both of us.
check whether they have stuck and
He assured us that we, like him,
If not today then tomorrow we are definitely going to work
These two cricket mental companions are great for all of us.
This is how they are guiding the whole of India
We are honored to work with your Excellency.
Whatever Amit Pathak has got, he has got it because of this.
Please be worse in the struggle of such great gurus
Along with this, my own is always
It is said that the first in his life and
Definitely without a plan, friends, no one
There is no need to adopt
always happens, especially in this business because
If we deviate even a little, we are as bad as the judge.
The more we deviate, the more our team also suffers.
If I started doing it, I would always do it from time to time, even today and
Always from the first day my seniors have given me
I was shown the way very well
Rakesh Jaiswal from Senior Square Kilometer
I would like to thank you I salute you
Apna Singh Yadav Shriprakash and spices
I would like to thank you and salute you
Once again to our Sirvi Ranjan Sir
I will start with these three lions for him
Taliban as thanks to the middle
I hope that you will
We must play Kali for the people because
Because of this, friends
Because of them, people like us never lose direction.
If you are not confused and are able to move forward
Thanks to your team along with minerals like
I will be happy if I work in the match.
I am the strongest, I don't get any happiness
There is even more to this
With many powerful forces behind me
Top is taking satsang with me today
Leaders who run their businesses with strong teams
I am promoting myself and leading the team
Do it and Atul Pathak ji is at the win level.
Neelam is making a great selection today.
Sanjeev ji, yes the farmer is on Strip Diamond
Leader is his Diamond Leader BC Pathak and
I have met many such Sahibs like Deenbandhu Sharma ji.
I told a lot of people that I
Everyone is introduced here, now let's talk about them
I won't be able to do it, but I definitely
I will also thank them as well
Because you guys trusted me
That's why I want to come forward in this business.
I got courage from such a leader who today
I can feel that I am working with such people.
I've been here with you for a while
I will keep some nasty things to myself by blocking the light
that I am in this business and my friends
Earlier I was like I told you that the middle
I belong to a class family and in that family
I want to see the game, Falguni, I am a small child
He was from the family but this happened to me
The problem was that I dreamed too big.
To see Shahdara is my thought from my family
a little different thing that we ate here
It is said that dreaming big is good.
Merit about living life that it
This thing was inside me from the beginning and because of this
I used to eat only very low in my house.
Tomorrow my thoughts were completely with my class and family.
My family used to say that it did not last.
Amit has been born in the wrong house many times.
I have not heard the dialogue and there is a lot in it.
He used to get angry but today he speaks from home.
Well then whatever it is, I'm always friends
In small things, meaning ordinary tasks
I never took an interest like you
It happens here too in America Family
It happens that I am told to go and
Put it on the electricity bill and deposit it online now
It happened out of pride, some 10, 12 years, 12 years
Think back to 15 years ago when I
I was a small Khan and I was also from a small town.
I was told to go and pay the electricity bill.
What did I ask if I would go there
If it wasn't there, who would stand in such a long line?
That the son-in-law of online friends is right now at that time
But what was my attitude that who
He will stand in such a long line and then he might accidentally walk away.
Did you also see that there was such a long line?
The counter from the new side used to go, thinking the container
So brother
Is today the last date or will you say yes now? This is the last date.
Where in the last date our India
You know, they pay all the bills.
If it happens then he said, whom should I call tomorrow in Patna and
Said late this will take 50 more Mars missions
I will drive, come home and ask father, father
I asked if the power went off and it was not that much of a problem.
There was a long line, who would join, either father or
He said that although the man looked like Cuban
If he is not a human being then I would have told him
Papa, you don't like all these things.
If he did, he would have said, why would he be thinking about you too?
that Amitabh Bachchan and Shahrukh Khan would follow the line
If they are there then he said that friend, these people are big
I am a star, which means I must be something.
Why do we even stand in line, this crazy girl?
He used to play, son, are you still understanding?
Now if there is a middle class family then such
to stay and give me some equal respect
Used to send for charge of vegetables
Whether it comes from the grocery store or smoke, it's mine.
This is that I will not do small things.
I won't bargain, I'll just go and buy it straight away.
If you were him son how many
What is this potato, I told you how much did it cost?
Why don't you take some of what's lying around?
A good alarm that goes off when you are late at home
Great interest in our family
How much money is left in the family?
Where is the famous saying that you can bargain with poverty?
I did what I liked or you would have said
Son wronged, fast people will be born tired
If you give money everywhere, will you be robbed?
I used to get scolded if I came. I was in General
I used to avoid tasks that I felt like it all
Where should I waste time on small tasks and
Turn off Yadav's mode and go to the grocery store.
Your anger was my system
I will go only when the Shukra is completely closed, why my
It seems like all this was happening
In the circle, my elder brother and I were four of us.
If we are brothers and sisters then I will do all this rubbish.
Elder brother Atul Bhaiya used to give it to his brother
I was quick to do these things but he
You won't be upset that he's doing all the garbage work
I gave it to him and he was very happy.
Because this snake-like World Cup match works
I also helped my elder brother in this business.
I gave them only what I got on this day
If you settle down, grow up with such a thought.
And I knew more about the truth of light
It was not known how our parents were women.
How to make a budget and run your household
When I was studying for the first time
Went to Madanpur with us during my student life
So, Chota Sarkar, we don't know much about it.
Was that you brand thing?
There are big luxury hotels
First and when Nagpur's Ratan Gurjar
The truth came out that in real money
What is the value or do people do so much for money?
Why bother saving?
I think when I went there, when
Saw the Yagya, saw the big shopping malls
When I saw luxury hotels, I became accustomed to
I entered a good hotel
I and the T-shirt will go to the shopping mall
etc. I saw it and liked it very well then
If you look at the bread, the rates mentioned are Rs 2000 per piece.
Time is not cheap to you
So what if the pin boys check it?
They say this is the cheapest, then I
I did yours and came back because ₹500
I used to get that you and by staying you can keep your
You will manage your expenses and take care of your food and drink.
What if I buy Malad friend's T-shirt?
I found out there's a hotel there.
Where big cricket stars are staying
I was fond of cricket till the player Sachin
Tendulkar is a big star like Ricky Ponting
What kind of hotel is Shahrukh, I will tell you everything.
He entered you there too, when you saw him
I'm fine in five-star hotels whenever I want.
When the meeting took place, he was handed the menu card.
He said, Sir, what would you like to say, ready?
By doing this it has become Rs 150-200, Rs 400
₹300 from here the rates of tea etc. copy start
Bay and Winner Hotel's protest was such that I
He said, if I take it, take it in your mind and completely
I would like a hotel but my stomach is not feeling well right now.
Just give me some water and I'll come back from there.
I wasn't looking at these things when I
When I reached the university, my seniors
Juniors used to guide me there.
I was doing the project bed height, I told him
I asked, Sir, you did that three-four years before me.
were big
Sir, did you see those branded items in those malls?
If you have done shopping in the showroom then you say it is ready.
Instead of making a ponytail, he keeps a lot of distance.
Murabba's hotel is yours where
Only when they are big stars, they would say something.
These were all the antics of the rich, don't stop at all
Wasn't a marauder but it tastes great
Seeing this, they used to say that these stupid people go away.
Yes, I give a lot of 65 marks to such places.
I thought I didn't want to spend any money.
that all these idiots are as close as me
You are earning money and then spending it on me.
They used to say that such a senior was the guide there.
Son, you have come to study, I am Amit
You should concentrate completely on your studies and the opposite.
Give me two more and you will do it well, so what?
The lights will be set, that's what we all hear
Also son, first go out properly.
Get injured and cannot come out properly
Yes, I have a very innocent question which is related to the country
It had come out that I asked him Sir, you are doing all this
If you have done it and left then say yes, all these deeds
He has now left as far as I know.
Gold at IIT Mumbai in Mumbai
He has also been a medalist and is a gold medalist
Moulasar you are a gold medalist that your
Life is set the way you want it to be
He fell silent, there was complete silence.
And he said, you should concentrate on your studies secretly.
I don't want to hurt them,
But really, if there was a bar in mind, who
People have so much money to move ahead in this world.
Why should I listen to what you are earning and what
You are giving me advice, you don't live your own life.
Let this be the life I envision
So when I left India I understood one thing.
I realized that our parents used it too much.
By sacrificing our stomachs, we would fulfil our dreams
Now I will do something in my life.
I didn't know how to do it
You didn't know the dense but this Tiger range
So far, I have made two things with my father's money.
Now I have spent my parents' money.
Who does this to do something on their own in life
And you can easily replace your friends with bicycles.
Got a fracture job in the university
Chanting for government job, everyone knows that smuggler
I have a lot of craze for Brahmin family.
It is like, hey, you got a job, everyone had made it.
With that friend, my life is set.
It's set up, so it's great.
I have slowly started having a good marriage.
If you don't like it then I will keep this thing liked.
I was worried that at that time the salary was Rs 5000.
Well, my dreams cannot be fulfilled with Rs 5,000.
You must be liking how it got set so I got my
I used to tell him, son, you should have been doing this for 10 years.
Even after 15 years, payment will be made and then we
Amla earns lakhs of rupees, Pooja is also in tyre
By the time it arrives, it will have reached great heights in literature.
I got worried that the income of lakhs of rupees
I dream of a good lifestyle
I will do this job and that job and I will get old
When I am done, I will get light and then that income
If I get it, I feel my life is set.
The big Jhaal is ruined but dies
What would he not do because we told him this
You had to do the work, you started working.
And in a life less promising, I
My friends have gone back to whom I loved dearly
If he wants, he can say it and not anything.
If you love him from your heart, the whole universe will love you.
She conspires to unite me and I came there only
I got a chance to come with my friends
I used to spend a lot of time with him, just singing songs earlier.
If I had to go out every evening, I would have died.
I will call my friend and ask where he is.
Then I found out that he was in front of my house.
Some people are sitting in someone's meeting at my house.
There was a 121 running in front of me just earning
I reached there and made flour and people
We are in talks and half the plan is done now.
I mean, these are some marketing people.
A little time for sisterly banter and a little meanness
He said that he was very fun loving and he used to stay ahead.
They should be given a little furnace.
The marketing people will show up in time.
He has started questioning it a bit from time to time.
The country is flour, all the good coats 45 were looted.
Speaking after every flight to earn income
Opportunity to earn income by taking this product
You will get it, it is very good, how little you have, brother
In the middle he mopped the house and told me, Sir, please take rest.
Understand the entire plan beforehand, then you
If he asks something, let's explain it to him.
Saw the Jaipur plan and after that when these
If there is a comprar part then suddenly when it tells that
Here you can see and take money within a week.
Tax checks come in thousands of rupees, that one for 2,000
1265 Work as you wish and you will get it
36 likes in Kota city ₹100 my brain
There should be no bloodshed there, friend, what kind of place is this?
Where such a big child's money is earned
I have the opportunity to immediately fill out the sign up form.
I did it and after coming home, how long could I continue working?
Why did I have to do this, there was so much money that
I managed to get some money from my sister after arranging it from here and there.
I invested some of my own money to set up a business.
And the one who showed the plan
Go and find him and kidnapper me
Why were you so busy, Chham had said that
Soon the Pandavas would remain in the snow for three-four days only.
I am not able to meet you, I can arrange your number for you.
There are people who call and go and find something.
There are those who leave after showing their sister.
Then friends, my beginning is very
It was a blast and I had a lot of fun
Started hitting such amazing fours and sixes
A lot of people think you don't
Do you know how I started my friends?
According to many people, only about
I talked to many people about this
That friend, business should be done very well.
Very good company, it gives the goods for the money
Think about getting money to buy and give people
I am involved after being told that something has to be done.
As 10 used to tell, one day, two days, three
In a day, in a month or two, my friends
Very good team of Zero along with T-20 team
There was someone with me, a collector, as much as I was.
I see everyone I talk to, friends and relatives
Am
This is the time when we become very
We lose patience quickly in this business.
When you come, you start dreaming big.
But he forgets, it's not my fault.
It happened but I showed a lot of patience.
People were worried until the work started.
The work that did not work in two days while speaking
Not running but vicious in two months
04 He was sent after me to get the system
No one ever stopped to tell me about
What is the training of that district?
I didn't know anything, just something according to my own understanding
Started talking to people
But in the meantime, I have a good habit that I
Only I Khedekar teaches all the seniors
Meena Book was a good habit by the grace of God
Reading habit friends, come to Safe Shop
I used to do a lot of book reading even before I got a job.
It was so from that point on its first
Robert Kiyosaki says that you are all someone you
You must know that we promote it.
It was written in it that whenever you like something
You will do different things whenever you are away from society.
If you do big work then people will initially
You won't understand, you'll laugh at me
If the matter is clear then WhatsApp something
Maybe that's why people don't understand
So take my words lightly.
But it's my job's fault it's theirs
The mistake is that temple when after two months I
It turned out that in some Czech on the way to
I saw someone only on the shoulder of an airplane
I had to show him that my work was not going well.
He said that you are planning
Do you hit me, tell me what is this?
The first time I met that person
Let me know about the training
Whatever happened in training in trading
I will tell you things and from there I will do my work.
Start with two people in the next one month
The area happened to me but that whole
One thing I understood from the training was that
If I want to do big work then this system
should come in and by really coming into the system
I will definitely tell you one thing,
Which also develops better than book reading habit
I am willing to learn at any cost.
If I was happy as per your wish then I would have seen you so much
If you learn good things then stay in that system.
Whoever started breaking here, senior actor
Read the entire company and then get complete details.
I came to know that friend, I talk to people who make lists like this.
If you do this, you will get two fittings in 3 months.
Once you understand the system, what is the use?
Now I'm not going my own way
If I do what the system was telling me, then I will do it in the next two
Meetings exceeded 50 in a month.
This system was counting two in 3 months
It is the strength of the system and
I've seen this system work every time.
Senior people should work and the system should definitely work
If it works, it's the system's job, not mine.
The business started and when I started working
If you start then you will lose a lot of time while working.
More on that side and friends regarding this matter
That I had come for myself, I had come for myself
I had taken it but the people I told in this business
I brought them in when the checks started coming in.
Let me tell you, I am so happy
My enthusiasm has increased many folds here.
I worry about my life at home
Don't do it here, some good add ons to others too.
can also make their life better
I can help you guys, how many people are there?
Those who are looking for good opportunities in the world
My enthusiasm for the product increased manifold and I
Getting even more excited when
Excited to work in
has started to do
Friends, when the first cheque of came in my life
There were about two hundred and fifty chapters at that time.
Directless pack, he had tweeted and said
That whatever check of 185 was there at that time, I had to delete it.
For fellows looking Czech 185's quite long
Only one in my life, when I found me
I was so excited that I got a check.
something like this dam 185 for those who
I think that work doesn't work, money doesn't come
If this bathroom works then it will work
Money definitely comes, I went with a passion in it
I am very confident that this will work for me
Just on Blue with excitement
You are a partner in starting work while working.
I helped my elder brother in this business.
At the beginning of trying to join
Interested because that bar already
Assistant Professor was a good college
When you were on post, I was your younger brother and you were mine
He used to take things lightly and also understand that
Time to understand this business.
I want to put the ID of the item I have
I knew you were in this house
Whatever their mistake did to you, your family members
My family doesn't understand either
They thought I had installed their ID when I was in Basti.
Now I was working for them too
If you get any benefit then put their ID again.
training was going on, that means Muzaffarpur and
I felt that I should somehow manage to save my elder brother.
I bring it into the system like pending work
How is it, what is it, if it happens to them too then
I took the vote in the sauce and a training cotton
By doing the things I do, click on them and make them business.
He was unable to invest in training.
Conway fell asleep and then he also went to the shop
After coming, he also started working and
After that, when you work, teach people.
And many times he did not listen to the conversation.
My senior Prakash has made an ad for this
Meet if you need to explain it to your team
The question always came to my mind, how to fix the team
So you can teach everyone through your work.
More knowledge is fine, both are good and more knowledge is also good
If you need more work, tell me if
If you collect regular cheques then your brother's
If there is a champion then I will regularly play five matches at that time.
210 is the baby hungry started my check
Taking this, Atul ji is very strong and he himself is
You were the obstructionist professor except
assistant introduction full time today winus level
But on which both of us brothers just give you full
It's time to move forward with the career you are pursuing.
Reasons for regular checks coming into the regular system
All this became possible and since then
My heart told me that you would never leave me
Otherwise I'll be almost 7 Diamonds before I get there.
No One Did a Strip Tanning Until 19
Even after that, whatever activity I have
This is the team of the senior school.
Where there is a need for something for almost 13 years now
Every meeting became more in full time and
The advantage of being active was that
Whatever achievements are being received and in this business
Friends, when you start working then one
Where does my commitment to purity come from?
What I mean by doing all this work inside is that I
The person who can't make the team
Bills for millions reached behind him
Something from my life which is only in my life
A huge turning point has been reached through
that I did a Makers voting Agra
I would wear you where my life resides
after going there friends after going there I
I saw how much respect Ahmed received.
I don't have money, people respect me so much, love me so much
People take decisions from there like shaking hands.
I took it and now only I
No one can stop you from becoming a diamond.
commitment to yourself that you just
Your first priority in my life
If only there will be no other commitment
It will not happen, but everything will be left behind.
Friends, you will not miss your success.
So if you say, the biggest reason behind this is
contribution that I decided that
Where people spent their entire life for 30 years.
in a limited middle class society
Work to earn a living to honor your family
I'm going to be doing this in the next three years.
At least Diamond must be purchased in the next three years.
I will take it and do whatever it takes
I will hand over everything to my team.
One is responsibility and the other is my own dreams.
I make my priority only
Stop setting up, dumb friends, I
I can always say this again in my life.
It is absolutely for me if
To say that after that when I had vision
It became clear when I saw such a big stage, I did this
Just look at the height of the bus, I just
I have not worked, I have worked only in
I haven't done it, I've only lived since then.
I have lived only for you, as I lived in the past.
with problem not a single day in my life
not only that but why did you not do this and something else
Saif will also be the priority.
Is
Many times such moments will come in your life too.
There are many ups and downs in my life too.
My life is in your hands
But what you need is your
difference in life so where do you want to ask
is it here that you
I remember one time I was training.
I had invested a lot
Click on Always Hold Meetings and Training
Did these A teams now have a lesson from Spain?
I had accepted that the mistakes that happened to me
It would be better if this drought does not happen in Britain
Positive attitude towards my seniors
He said you should always be positive
I saw that everyone has a good thing in them but something is missing.
There are the same people around me too
Cut the cheese line of the joint tax
His only drawback was that after
I haven't noticed anything, but I
It should be a good thing and not a swan's.
What is saying that good it takes shortcomings
If he leaves us then such people are also with us
I thought it must be my mistake.
The name of each one of the thousand people joining
People Bloody Mobile Number Note in My Diary
I used to want to join someone
After the training was told that
NOT ANY PERSONAL OR PRODUCT THAT
No because I have wrong product address also.
I had defeated him once, so this was a mistake.
Now come to the network and teach me
If not at that time then in the beginning Yogi
I was not attached to my senior.
The path which brings light to a good destination
But before I could reach them
Do something very soon to fix this
If this had happened then I could have had a meeting with them.
Give one doctor for every thousand people
Friends, death of any person is expensive.
I will never let him down, ...
I will not let you feel it and after so much promotion
The reason was that when gold was created all this
My voice recognition was meher soil
I promote to water every person
I still promote the system today
Because we all are here because of this system
The solution was made that same week. 240
People attended the tanning session with my team.
And there will be eight or ten people who have double ID.
The system benefits from this strength
And I was talking about my priorities.
So in my house, the one who is my dearest means
It so happens that the one from whom we are most
The one you love the most
So an incident with my nephew, I thought
Something like this happened, he had a problem with me since childhood.
He loved them very much
The child had to be admitted to the hospital
Little child and this situation of peers
The doctor said there was no hope now.
No, I mean I raised my hands and gave two
Day after day I had my training alarms
Juniors gave me the time of Titanic
I was completely heartbroken when I called.
I was thinking of refusing to attend training.
What will I take? I am disappointed inside and I call
After doing this, I told the junior that if the driver
Immediately he said the city such a great promotion
What should I tell you when so much is happening with the mask?
We thought that there was a loss
Friends, it will seem like your training is a promotion.
Four hundred and fifty people are confirmed with him.
After that I stopped for mushrooms and I
He said okay I'm coming, that's what I thought.
Whatever problem my friends have
Depending on the problem, a chance of what is wrong
Why didn't I tell them that I am committed to you?
which why why a little bit
I went there tanning these friends at that time
When my most beloved thing is gone from my life
She was going and she went like this
The old man found out that he was my nephew.
But I did this training there and my
I could not tell everyone by hiding my troubles.
Motivated people a lot that day
I was just passionate about improving myself.
I spoke
Because I understood that many things are ours
Karma is not in your hands but in God's
At least we can do the minimum given in our hands.
Do it right and I clicked on it.
So I only ever gave advice on May Day.
There have been many occasions when there have been big
We could have easily made excuses and walked away.
But I never did, I always said
No, I have got it only because of this trust.
I can tell the doctor less matches than
It will cost money, don't worry, don't give any alarm.
I'll just do my work without saying
So I have the least amount of gold.
At least it only makes laptops.
Literature has to make many such sacrifices.
There is in life but what happens with that?
What happens with that is I can do that
Some changes may be taking place in your life.
No problem, don't worry, you will have many things
I will have to give up friendship all my birthdays
Party says everything for 3 years until
I will just say diamond, I will not do anything else.
My favourite sport is cricket
If I ever leave cricket, then the next day
I have exams, so there is no restriction on me playing cricket.
I can't keep going at a young age.
I joined for 14 years every day
I used to play cricket but only after coming to
Later I had pledged to my seniors
That the new companionship has changed my life in 3 years and
I spent three years and then picked up my back.
I did not see it, I said the first diamond is closed
It took me a while to become a diamond.
Ahmed was six months into his three and a half years
Company which makes such small sacrifices but
Today I can say whatever revolt I get
The rewards you get from your teammates in the wash
The little oppression you take in front of him
You and the birthday party are the priority
When Shadi leaves Vyas's house, he
I could get a safe here today
too much is too big
I missed the weddings of many friends at that time.
Before Diamond, I was my maternal uncle's son's son.
I left the marriage because if I go, my
I will miss my team and support.
If the train is missed, then many times they say that
He doesn't go to anyone's wedding.
They used to say that no one would come to the wedding.
I called you my senior sir, I am completely
I am giving you tips, that's why I said this.
My only concern is that it hasn't worked for you.
Yes, this is only for you, my senior.
Alarm that shows how many friends you have every 2025
Song and what did you say, become a diamond
Your members and playwrights will be there and he
Many hopefuls and friends, today again
have you been friends with me when you could
It happened when I became successful, after that to me
By clicking on the people function you will keep which
Will be on a date but not respected before that
Remember Milti, as long as you are all right
Before that people will ask you where are you?
But your property does not have light time.
If he wants it, what happened to him friends, complete him
A huge change in my life and what I
I'll show you
What has happened with this, friends?
There has been such a big change in my life
That injury exam beginners friends
I used to dream I wish I had
to bike
During college days, notes used to come in bikes.
It used to come from my heart, I wish I had
You can take the bike to your
First Mothers, well, many days ago
But I was very happy that Arya I
I did something on my own that I am the first
I have a lot of space for the bike and I also have a lot of feeling.
I'm glad that I don't think about it in my house
It could have been that there were four brothers and sisters, any of us
If you want to buy a bicycle then ladies also buy it.
I used to take a bicycle because my sisters also rode it.
I'll find I'm the youngest in my family
So my whole self is for myself or for someone else.
If you want to buy a normal bike then buy this
P used to say that he would tag me because everything went well.
First, it's clear that thanks to this, I am on my own.
But I bought my bike first and then my laptop.
I took a wrapped bike, then two more bikes.
I went and got a laptop, after that the laptop and
Now his mobiles etc. are gone.
You can count your wings, yes, it certainly is possible.
After coming into this snake today and
Branded like Apple is with us
I am using a brand like Apple.
The income that he earns in 2 years in a whole year
After doing the job he took the mobile with him, the thief
Earn lakhs of rupees just by the power of this
If you had spent 2-3 years with us, the small ones
If we just give you the dress from here then it is like this
Big brains are waiting for us
While working in my house, I just
My uncle and father were working in the district.
I met him and took the second one but
I said, Papa, it's just me.
And when I left my job, my father handed me the
My father was a little upset and said
The Amit, if you have got a job then work in the job
I just leave it and do whatever I have to do.
If you want to do it then do it to Papa ji.
I had told you, Paaji, that when you retire, you will be separate.
Talk Chana in the evening at three thirty to four
I will tell you in which direction then you will
A broken bike or a fabulous one of your own
What if a father bought a car from his earnings?
I will say that son is busy with his work.
I would love to go, my friends, and my family too.
They don't refuse us, they don't know how much
We work with great quality
When it has to be shown, they also support.
I said, Papa ji, job is possible only in
It is not possible for me, now give me half a chance
I will give you a confident match and you will feel proud.
I had my first coffee just from the
Papa ji's retirement day was three and a half.
four times a week or two after that
I bought it a week ago, so which one else should I buy?
A few days later, I also met Diamond.
If it had been complete, Papa ji would have proudly said
I was telling the employee there that this was mine
Son works with his own earnings from his fragrance
I want to tell you my friends about the happiness on his face.
This is the biggest achievement for me.
My parents were very happy with me
Only in the Parliament did they see their own happiness
I thought we were done living with him.
Later the series continued and then Hyundai
Otherwise I have a great car, I said next
Black so it's your turn to start her
Baad minister so many dams unlimited ho
Pimples do not harm the eyes due to pendants.
Limited and go by number go away
So I got such a great car there, otherwise
Sex in your country which was my dream that lakh
It was my dream that I would earn Rs.
I achieved an income of lakhs of rupees at the age of 62.
I had done the embroidery on the ball.
and before that a tweet
I was in a daze until my senior said that I would chat.
Why didn't it become so, I would have put it now
I will tell you so that no one makes the mistake again.
If I am there then don't do it, I had a problem with it.
When the cheque was not prepared for a week, my senior said
That Amit ji has said all the checks as per the book.
How much dedicated check made put in the house
Sir, I left it, he understood something was wrong.
Actually he was from Sydney, so what?
This thing should be your check
about your serial
don't worry about me
whirl and swirl
If it's not your job, it's not yours
Junior's check should be made
It's down to those who made the check.
Flying sapphire, for which the doctor made a check
make a check and make a check
Don't be a coward
become and by motivating him and this is our
Ghaghra
It's very wrong to work
If the ghee is at fault then I
I am speaking
There are trees about him that in life
Check mine sometime after that it got interesting
No, this is my first time earning one lakh in 2 years.
Vikram introduced that ever since in life
Also worked through millions of passwords
There was no weakness, hence the journey to success.
He is progressing rapidly and excelling at his exams.
Diamond working on his target
It was good for me only, I saw it
that the diamonds were carried on elephants
I dreamed of being respected by kings
I saw you also want me to weather
Clear system from peers, follow senior
What happened was that I was very young.
Why did I take all the achievements in
From diamonds to weekly years of age
Ahmed was the youngest at that time.
Completed and if you get this achievement
So what happens if you get this achievement?
Why Bilaspur is the best colony?
I am buying my 4bhk in the density of black.
I bought a bungalow where my family lives.
And very wonderful jo rule torch light this
After coming into my own, like I
I used to go to hotels, well, two of those places.
I used to see how the interior shop reaches here.
Taking a photo, the highest pillow is all
It must be felt that the wife is an interior designer.
Spend the entire money and get the best out of your laptop.
I am busy with reply photos, now it's enough
All other updates have been made
That all this was told by his friends during his 29 years.
I had done it earlier which is showing all the things
is the first house, then the second house and the third
Home and many properties are an investment that
The photo of the house you are seeing is from the movie
If I used to see it, I would think that I wish it was like this
My houses which go inside and
He would say that a dream comes true.
If we keep working, no matter how hard we work
Do it and get a reward so high that
Hard work, no time, no merit
I see people in literature, but everywhere else.
I do so much work only if I work that much
If you do anything with so many dividers
My son doesn't feel like working hard today in Bilaspur
studies in the best school in
This snake is found in Brilliant Public School.
Because if I really had a job, I would never
It was not possible that I was in such a school.
Because studying in CSP is worth lakhs of rupees.
It doesn't matter but thanks app thanks
Seniors thanks my team for such an open
I will get the setting today in the highest school
I am there and I want to share this with you.
I would like to do this, my dream is very big
The dream was fulfilled
to Ajay
of Jhaal
[Appreciation]
has happened
[music]
do it
has happened
[Appreciation]
do it
has happened
and references
That's the third Mercedes car I bought and very
Increased power friends, apart from just such
He is a big industry or businessman.
looked closely at military reforms but
I just saw that you are also a common man like me.
You can take three more good things
If you have cut into the new business of your friends
But I am also continuously in the team.
I called everyone within 15 days of my
The business which elder brother Atul Pathak ji started
Junior and delivery guys, this business
It has the power to make people never drive this car in their life.
Thinking of taking written thanks, just thanks
Support system thanks mental that 15 days
Inside a Mercedes a positive of our house
stood in front and
That is why friends, whatever I am talking about luxury life
I used to think that I wish they met in the hotel
Life came back today after being declared dead
Five in such places is part of the style
Star Hotel Pearl Wherever you go, five
Opportunity to stay at Vansh Property from Star
May that child receive health
The whole family is going to the match today.
I love my family more
It is good that I want to give it every year
Twice, thrice, where is the best place to visit?
I can go on a fast with the trust and
The photo you are seeing is the best
Good hotels are his hotels where I
I can stop and just a while ago areas
some time before, taking 27 people
Kashmir's tip if very concerned about family
Happy family wherever the side goes
It's not just now, it's almost past in life
1070 Flight wherever there is an aircraft
Don't go for this lifestyle friends, stay safe.
Why do you show this photo in the shop?
What is the purpose, you can understand it a little bit.
Will understand the purpose behind showing this photo
This is what Amit Pathak has done, this is it
But there is a greater purpose than that, which is with the address
What I want to show you is that if you put your
Look at the photos and see this for your family.
Everything to you too because I get the same opportunity
It has been found and Sir, you have found it and we
So it took some time, but nowadays the company
The company has updated its products.
Pran, may you get all these things sooner
It is about to happen, click and share it with your seniors and
I always enjoy spending time with the team.
If I get a chance regularly, I
You should work with your seniors or with the team.
I will meet you anywhere, travels within the country and abroad
Travel abroad approximately one point per year
My family gets fixed a lot.
Happy just in case you can see it when
Action is yours for just one day
My family is very happy ever since.
Parliament and Diamond were made only in me because
There are plenty of facilities for them today.
I see people that after getting educated their children
Your parents are living abroad
When the elderly are in need of care,
We are not able to find them and when we need them the most
Some are going to America and some are here
lives in Bangalore but
If proof that I just in the tips letter
Diwa when my parents need me
I have got so much business freedom, so their
The bread made by their hands is still available for them
After eating, I moved ahead taking his blessings.
I am growing today when they need me today
All the comforts in my house are provided by the driver.
From the car to cooking
That they have a timetable for everything, including the child.
Everyone, including the elderly, is a happy family today.
So the only reason is so much love
Friends, maybe you can earn money from it.
It is not that only your money comes
There may be something more wonderful, but that is freedom.
You will never get that freedom that you
Take it from everyone and the biggest thing is that the love
We will get it from the team and the system.
We can't even imagine all this.
Friends, let me tell you that you should think about
Your welcome will be even better than this.
Your welcome is going to be just as wonderful
It's just me and the five directors.
I had a meeting with you. Now I am going to tell you this.
I feel very proud meaning
That I, who am a different set top leader of the company
You're looking for company for gents
Direct selling is elegant all five
Apart from the director, you can see the top leaders.
Stay with them to meet me
opportunity to attend meetings and
It was because of our seniors that I was able to
I found companionship with people I considered worthy of.
It is a matter of luck that now the state is in their hands
Eliminate all the negative things in life
You give only and only the girl Disha
Practice makes his life crazy millions
People also have their own, I just did some small
Pay attention to things that your family
I've always loved that eighty-four million
After the vagina, the companions get human life
Maya is attained after passing through eighty-four lakh births.
Never treat this life like common insects
I can't live like this so I'm by myself
I love my family very much, whoever
This person loves his family
Guaranteed you will never take this snake lightly.
I will not take my uncle's name from my family.
People who truly love themselves
I love you in two ways
The boy tells the girl but hey to himself
Love yourself, if you love yourself now
You will give yourself a normal life.
Lots of love for your family and yourself
I have never compromised in my life
So from here on in vision always
It is clear that the cat also has a big job to do.
at a sum that was once as large as a full dot
I moved away and never used any other company.
Kabir, I have stopped listening to the plan and told it to you.
What else is there to do without going and seeing that once
There will be success by using knowledge leadership.
People who are always on the move and
Well, I have seen that for so many years
No one is happy to be going there
Not satisfied but believed and
But only the first and last cum touched my
We will remain the best company
I have already received quality
Told that always only you will be with me first
You have given me priority by giving me that love
You have improved your entire lighting very well.
Alarm set rough drafting my dreams
It's my business, so the responsibility is mine.
I can't rely on anyone else
Even the senior did not call and say this.
Pranami ji, you are not at work and you win.
Why doesn't Amrit come to give his team
Work together because I take responsibility for it.
Always ready to take many people
I have to call again and again, hey you in the morning
Do this in the meeting and in the evening in the field
Ignore it, but I will never take this thing
By not giving your senior an opportunity to speak
I have to say that you motivate
Why not role responsibility regarding price?
Why are you not taking it for your friends?
Always check on your leaders so my very
focused more and that was the reason
I had 3 toes with me when we made the roll.
My three rubies made my diamond
Along with me and my mother-in-law,
Excessive Passion for Achievement
I have worked as a
If any leader did all the work then his business
has the greatest interest in pursuing
If we want to expand our business then no one
There is no question how our business is not
I have to read and the book is Vitamin A
Wait, tell me if this was a video, I mean, business.
I would have dealt with the first two, but the pain came first.
But because of that I look at myself
I am an unusual boy, I just became a leader
So this is definitely very useful in between.
Everyone must adopt this *
The Bloody Mary was very good and I
antire country pukara and se proper agar ke
So always keep a line of good books
I promote following active
He already said that it was round so two hundred and fifty people went to Tilak
Time came friends 40 people mother very much
Promoted this step is followed that
This is what people want to do with business and new notes.
Tell the police to fulfill a new dream brother
Doing the same old work is becoming the same old work
The same old thing will happen which Sanjay Jain is doing.
Great nursing done by Ross
It was that Rakesh Chandra's work was the same, there was no new work.
But attention is most important to your new whole
If they are cigarettes, this tape will be time course
I worked very hard and
People have taken this initiative very much on this
Loving people to work with
Which is the most important thing in business?
He has followed this one too much, that blot
For those in the five provinces who are friends
Part pinks are working where the part
Time is running low, it can be a paan for that
But if we want to make a career full time then
10:00 Even if you show the plant 15 times, it is less.
The more you show, the better
And when I went to Gurukul and other training
Attended the first train that was formed
Rajat Sir's photo in Agra at a five star hotel
I got it from there and I understood this
How to develop leadership skills in business
This is how our thinking develops correctly.
And after taking such training, definitely
In reality, there are many people in the soil who speak
Sir, only after going into this category we
Our gram flour was clear, our technique
We were all behind Mega Shop friends Naseem
attended but worked in such a manner
Did you ever know that there used to be a Soni in Chhattisgarh?
were tanning this do like big big so you
Three people with me would have seen Tejasvita
There were only two people under Rajat Sir's training.
New Neelam Sanjeev That Triple Diamond is number
I am three, so three of us sat down.
All three Diamonds were late for their first show.
Why have we become diamonds, still we are doing this
Chhattisgarh is playing cricket for the first time
I did this under the guidance of my senior and
I'm always trying to set a record.
Bringing more and more people into the Amrit system
how will you go so this is the best record that
By hitting back to back 300 for your team clockwise
I had cleared my system and PIN.
With the help of this, the curtain is revealed by this team of friends.
is constantly increasing, continuously increasing
And by doing these basic tasks, my
It can happen so that you have to repeatedly
Senior singers, many of you must be doing it.
If you are improving then I will say this about this work.
Regularisation of salary and shift work
By giving first priority to your
If you wish to make yourself special among the common people
If so, then definitely
So I daresay I seem very small to you
I know that I see Sanjay Jain Sir today.
And I keep nursing everyone, Madhav Sir
I see Jasvir Sir, Deveshwar in these
People have questioned such a big milestone
In the last way, what should I say about their own name?
Friends, I see their achievements.
We will definitely get all the achievements from you all.
You should stop your talk here.
I would like to once again heartily congratulate all of you.
I would like to thank you that you played the role very well Sunidhi
It was nice to share the request with you guys.
Once again great man Narsinghgarh WhatsApp
Many many salutations to you Sir, you have given me this.
Thank you for speaking, Sir
Thank you, Pathak ji, I will tell you about the soil.
It is a gift for
123 send current movie
[music]
has happened
So please subscribe na koi